<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Gregor Stiglic</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gregor Stiglic is a vice-dean for research, associate professor and head of Research Institute at the Faculty of Health Sciences, University of Maribor (FHS UM). He worked on numerous national and international projects in bioinformatics and healthcare informatics. Gregor was the co-founder of the Bioinformatics master study programme at the FHS UM in 2008. He also worked as a Visiting Researcher at Data Analysis and Biomedical Analytics (DABI) Center at Temple University (2012) and as a Visiting Assistant Professor at Shah Lab, Stanford School of Medicine, Stanford University (2013).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His research interests encompass machine learning techniques with application to healthcare. Specific areas of his technical interest include comprehensibility of predictive models, human interaction based classification, stability of feature selection algorithms, meta-learning and longitudinal rule discovery. His work was published in multiple conferences, journals and books. Gregor gave talks on his knowledge discovery in healthcare and bioinformatics research at renowned research institutions such as IBM T.J. Watson Research Center, Stanford University, University of Manchester, University of Edinburgh and University of Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He served as a co-organizer of the series of Workshops on Data Mining for Medicine and Healthcare held in conjunction with SIAM SDM 2013 (Austin, TX, USA), 2014 (Philadelphia, PA, USA), 2015 (Vancouver, BC, Canada), 2016 (Miami, FL, USA) and 2017 (Houston, TX, USA). Gregor also served as a co-organizer of the series of Workshops on Data Mining for Medical Informatics held in conjunction with the American Medical Informatics Association (AMIA) Annual Symposiums in 2014 (Washington, DC), 2015 (San Francisco, CA) and 2016 (Chicago, IL). He also served as a program chair of the Analytics Track at the 2016 IEEE International Conference on Healthcare Informatics held in Chicago, IL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gregor is an associate editor of BMC Medical Informatics and Decision Making (Nature Springer), editorial board member of Artificial Intelligence in Medicine (Elsevier), PLoS ONE (Public Library of Science), Journal of Healthcare Informatics Research (Nature Springer) and has also served as a guest editor for Special Issue on Data Mining in Medicine and Healthcare in Data Mining and Knowledge Discovery journal (Nature Springer).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
